A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 100 International - Series 253 Washington FA387a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United States, 1929-1977; 200; 113 box(es)
  - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1947-1979; 200.R; 88 Cubic Feet; 220 __Boxes __88 cubic feet
    - Pratt Institute - Lehmann-Haupt, Hellmut - (Art and Government Study), 1955-1957 (Box 405, Folder 3497)
    - Prausnitz, Frederick - (Contemporary Music), 1965-1967 (Box 405, Folder 3498)
    - Princeton University - American Civilization - (Program Development), 1943-1944 (Box 405, Folder 3499)
    - Princeton University - American Civilization - (Program Development), 1945-1947, 1952 (Box 406, Folder 3500)
    - Princeton University - American Civilization - (Program Development), 1945-1947, 1952 (Box 406, Folder 3501)
    - Princeton University - American Civilization - Reports, 1943-1945, 1947-1948; 31 items contained in folders 3501A-3502. (Box 406, Folder 3501A)
    - Princeton University - American Civilization - Reports, 1943-1945, 1947-1948; 31 items contained in folders 3501A-3502. (Box 406, Folder 3502)
    - Princeton University - American Civilization - Wertenbaker, Thomas J., 1944-1946, 1949-1953 (Box 406, Folder 3503)
    - Princeton University - Blackmur, R.P. - (Travel Grants, Europe and Near East), 1951-1955 (Box 406, Folder 3504)
    - Princeton University - Butow, Robert J.C. - (Biography of Hideki Tojo), 1954, 1956-1961 (Box 406, Folder 3505)
    - Princeton University - Duberman, Martin - (History of Black Mountain College), 1967-1970 (Box 406, Folder 3506)
    - Princeton University - Great Power Diplomacy - (Conference), 1951, 1953 (Box 406, Folder 3507)
    - Princeton University - Index of Christian Art, 1936-1939 (Box 406, Folder 3508)
    - Princeton University - Index of Christian Art, 1949, 1952-1953 (Box 407, Folder 3509)
    - Princeton University - Kaufmann, Walter - (Contemporary Philosophy), 1955, 1957, 1970-1974 (Box 407, Folder 3510)
    - Princeton University - Literary Criticism, 1947-1957, 1963 (Box 407, Folder 3511)
    - Princeton University - Literary Criticism, 1947-1957, 1963 (Box 407, Folder 3512)
    - Princeton University - Literary Criticism, 1947-1957, 1963 (Box 407, Folder 3513)
    - Princeton University - Military History, 1951-1953 (Box 407, Folder 3514)
    - Princeton University - Mirsky, Jeannette - (Biography of Sir Mark Aurel Stein), 1963-1968 (Box 407, Folder 3515)
    - Princeton University - Mitchell, Richard P. - (Muslim Brotherhood), 1955-1957 (Box 407, Folder 3516)
    - Princeton University - Murty, K.S. - (Travel Grant), 1958-1960 (Box 408, Folder 3517)
    - Princeton University - Musical Research - (Electronic Music), 1964-1967 (Box 408, Folder 3518)
    - Princeton University - Near Eastern Studies, 1944-1964 (Box 408, Folder 3519)
    - Princeton University - Near Eastern Studies, 1944-1964 (Box 408, Folder 3520)
    - Princeton University - Near Eastern Studies, 1944-1964 (Box 408, Folder 3521)
    - Princeton University - Near Eastern Studies, 1944-1964 (Box 408, Folder 3522)
    - Princeton University - Near Eastern Studies, 1944-1964 (Box 408, Folder 3523)
    - Princeton University - Near Eastern Studies - (Supplementary Material), 1948, 1958-1959 (Box 409, Folder 3524)
    - Pro Arte Symphony - Orchestra - (Contemporary Music), 1969-1972 (Box 409, Folder 3525)
    - Purdue University - Gass, William - (Creative Writing), 1964-1969, 1971 (Box 409, Folder 3526)
    - Purdue University - Haworth, Lawrence - (Travel Grant, Urban Planning), 1959-1963 (Box 409, Folder 3527)
    - Purdy, James - (Novelist, Support), 1967-1969 (Box 409, Folder 3528)
    - Queens College - McElroy, Joseph P. - (Novelist, Support), 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 409, Folder 3529)
    - Radcliff College - Valentine, Jean - (Poet), 1965-1966, 1968-1969 (Box 409, Folder 3530)
    - Reck, David - (Travel Grant, Composer), 1966-1970, 1976 (Box 409, Folder 3531)
    - Renan, Sheldon - (Contemporary Film-Makers), 1966-1968 (Box 409, Folder 3532)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth - (Travel Grant, Theatre in Europe and Far East), 1966-1968 (Box 410, Folder 3533)
    - Reynolds, Roger Lee - (Composer), 1964-1968 (Box 410, Folder 3534)
    - Reynolds, Roger Lee - (Composer), 1964-1968 (Box 410, Folder 3535)
    - Ribman, Ronald B. - (Playwright), 1965-1969 (Box 410, Folder 3536)
    - Rogoff, Gordon - (Travel Grant, Theatre Critic), 1968-1969 (Box 410, Folder 3537)
    - Rutgers University - Abel, Lionel - (Creative Writing), 1964-1966, 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 410, Folder 3538)
    - Rutgers University - American History - (McKitrick, Eric), 1958-1960 (Box 410, Folder 3539)
    - Rutgers University - Contemporary Chamber Ensemble, 1963-1966 (Box 410, Folder 3540)
    - Rutgers University - Contemporary Chamber Ensemble, 1963-1966 (Box 410, Folder 3541)
    - Rutgers University - Contemporary Chamber Ensemble, 1967-1969 (Box 411, Folder 3542)
    - Rutgers University - Latin American Literature - (Translations), 1957-1961 (Box 411, Folder 3543)
    - Rutgers University - Mexican Drama - (Carballido, Emilio), 1961-1962 (Box 411, Folder 3544)
    - Rutgers University - Myers, Gordon - (Early American Music), 1968-1971 (Box 411, Folder 3545)
    - Rutgers University - Polite, Carlene - (Creative Writing), 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 411, Folder 3546)
    - Rutgers University - Sontag, Susan - (Creative Writing), 1964-1967 (Box 411, Folder 3547)
    - Sacramento State College - Bankowsky, Richard J. - (Creative Writing), 1966-1969 (Box 411, Folder 3548)
    - Saint Louis University - Knoepfle, John - (Poet), 1966-1969 (Box 411, Folder 3549)
    - Saint Louis Symphony Orchestra - Young Composers Program, 1962-1964 (Box 411, Folder 3550)
    - Saint Louis Symphony Orchestra - Young Composers Program, 1965-1969 (Box 412, Folder 3551)
    - Saint Louis Symphony Orchestra - Young Composers Program, 1965-1969 (Box 412, Folder 3552)
    - Saint Vladimir's Orthodox Theological Seminary, 1949-1954 (Box 412, Folder 3552A)
    - Saint Vladimir's Orthodox Theological Seminary - Reprints, 1951-1953; 5 Items (Box 412, Folder 3553)
    - San Francisco Art Association - Information Center, 1958-1962 (Box 412, Folder 3554)
    - San Francisco Art Association - Information Center - Catalogues, 1958-1959 (Box 412, Folder 3555)
    - San Francisco Ballet Guild, 1955 (Box 412, Folder 3556)
    - Folder Number 3557 NOT USED (Box 413, Folder 3557)
    - San Francisco Ballet Guild, 1956-1962, 1964 (Box 413, Folder 3558)
    - San Francisco Ballet Guild, 1956-1962, 1964 (Box 413, Folder 3559)
    - San Francisco Museum of Art - Public School Program, 1954-1962, 1965 (Box 413, Folder 3560)
    - San Francisco Museum of Art - Public School Program, 1954-1962, 1965 (Box 413, Folder 3561)
    - San Francisco State College - Contemporary Music, 1965-1966 (Box 413, Folder 3562)
    - San Francisco State College - Morris, Wright - (Creative Writing), 1964-1968 (Box 413, Folder 3563)
    - San Francisco State College - Poetry Center, 1955-1961 (Box 413, Folder 3564)
    - San Francisco Symphony Orchestra - Young Composers Program, 1966-1969 (Box 413, Folder 3565)
    - San Francisco Tape Music Center, Inc., 1965 (Box 413, Folder 3566)
    - San Jose State College - Roberts, Paul - (Teaching English in Egypt), 1956-1957 (Box 414, Folder 3567)
    - Sands, Dorothy - (Turkish National Conservatory), 1956-1959 (Box 414, Folder 3568)
    - Sarah Lawrence College - Aeolian Chamber Players, 1965-1970 (Box 414, Folder 3569)
    - Sarah Lawrence College - Jordan, June - (Poet), 1967-1972 (Box 414, Folder 3570)
    - Sarah Lawrence College - Loewenberg, Bert James - (Historiography of U.S.), 1948-1950, 1963 (Box 414, Folder 3571)
    - Sarah Lawrence College - MacNiece, Louis - (Playwriting in Verse), 1954-1955 (Box 414, Folder 3572)
    - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Congress of Strings, 1964-1968, 1970 (Box 414, Folder 3573)
    - Schickel, Richard - (D.W. Griffith Biography), 1969-1971 (Box 414, Folder 3574)
    - Schneider, Alan - (Travel Grant, Theater in Eastern Europe), 1967-1969 (Box 414, Folder 3575)
    - Schurz, William Lytle - (Travel Grant, Brazilian History), 1958-1959 (Box 414, Folder 3576)
    - Scripps College - Printing Techniques - (Purchase of Equipment), 1952-1954, 1956 (Box 415, Folder 3577)
    - Seattle Repertory Theatre, 1963-1965 (Box 415, Folder 3578)
    - Seattle Repertory Theatre - MacDonald, Pirie - (Director) - (Grant in Aid), 1966-1969 (Box 415, Folder 3579)
    - Seattle Symphony Orchestra - Composer in Residence - (Hovhaness, Alan), 1965-1969 (Box 415, Folder 3580)
    - Seattle Symphony Orchestra - Young Composers Program, 1963-1968 (Box 415, Folder 3581)
    - Seattle Symphony Orchestra - Young Composers Program, 1963-1968 (Box 415, Folder 3582)
    - Seattle Symphony Orchestra - Young Composers Program, 1963-1968 (Box 415, Folder 3583)
    - Seattle Symphony Orchestra - Young Composers Program, 1963-1968 (Box 415, Folder 3584)
    - Semantics Conference, Monterey, 1949-1951 (Box 416, Folder 3585)
    - Semantics Conference, Monterey - Arrangements, 1950 (Box 416, Folder 3586)
    - Sewanee Review - (Creative Writing Fellowships), 1943-1958 (Box 416, Folder 3587)
    - Sewanee Review - (Creative Writing Fellowships), 1943-1958 (Box 416, Folder 3588)
    - Sewanee Review - (Creative Writing Fellowships), 1943-1958 (Box 416, Folder 3589)
    - Sewanee Review - Spears, Monroe K. - (Travel Grant, India and Great Britain), 1955-1956 (Box 416, Folder 3590)
    - Sharon Creative Arts Foundation - (Young People's Workshop), 1966-1967 (Box 416, Folder 3591)
    - Shapiro, Harvey - (Creative Writing, Poetry), 1967-1968 (Box 416, Folder 3592)
    - Sheed, Wilfred - (Creative Writing, Fiction), 1967-1969 (Box 417, Folder 3593)
    - Shepard, Sam - (Playwright), 1965-1972 (Box 417, Folder 3594)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - (Philipse Family Papers) - (Jacob Judd and Agnes Gilchrist), 1958-1960 (Box 417, Folder 3595)
    - Smith, Carlton Sprague - (Music in America before 1700), 1955 (Box 417, Folder 3596)
    - Smith College - Garrigue, Jean - (Creative Writing, Poetry and Non-Fiction), 1966 (Box 417, Folder 3597)
    - Smith College - Powers, James F. - (Creative Writing, Fiction), 1965-1968 (Box 417, Folder 3598)
    - Smithsonian Institution - Chinese Art - (Photographing Project), 1955-1963, 1965 (Box 417, Folder 3599)
    - Society of American Historians - (History and the Media), 1949-1953 (Box 417, Folder 3600)
    - Society of American Historians - (History and the Media), 1949-1953 (Box 417, Folder 3601)
    - Society of American Historians - (History and the Media), 1949-1953 (Box 417, Folder 3602)
    - Society of Biblical Literature - (Critical Apparatus to the New Testament), 1948-1953, 1955 (Box 418, Folder 3603)
    - Society of Biblical Literature - (Critical Apparatus to the New Testament), 1948-1953, 1955 (Box 418, Folder 3604)
    - Society for Japanese Studies - Japanese Art - (Eaton, Alan), 1947-1955 (Box 418, Folder 3605)
    - Society for Strings, Inc. - Teacher Training - (Galamian, Ivan), 1966-1971 (Box 418, Folder 3606)
    - Sokolow, Anna - (Lyric Theatre Company), 1969-1970 (Box 418, Folder 3607)
    - Sorell, Walter - (Dance Critic), 1968-1970 (Box 418, Folder 3608)
    - South Asian Studies, 1954-1955 (Box 418, Folder 3609)
    - South Asian Studies, 1954-1955 (Box 418, Folder 3610)
    - South Asian Studies, 1956-1962, 1964 (Box 419, Folder 3611)
    - South Asian Studies, 1956-1962, 1964 (Box 419, Folder 3612)
    - South Asian Studies, 1956-1962, 1964 (Box 419, Folder 3613)
    - South Asian Studies, 1956-1962, 1964 (Box 419, Folder 3614)
    - South Asian Studies - Newsletter, 1955-1958 (Box 419, Folder 3615)
    - South Asian Studies - Supplementary Material, 1961 (Box 419, Folder 3616)
    - South Asian Language Studies - (Consultants), 1952-1954, 1956 (Box 420, Folder 3617)
    - Southern California School of Theology - Ross, Floyd H. - (Travel Grant, Japan), 1957-1961 (Box 420, Folder 3618)
    - Southern Illinois University - Community Development - (Poston, Richard W.), 1959-1964 (Box 420, Folder 3619)
    - Southern Illinois University - Performing Company - (Dunham, Katherine), 1970-1971 (Box 420, Folder 3620)
    - Southern Illinois University - Performing Company - Proposal, 1970 (Box 420, Folder 3621)
    - Southern Regional Council, Inc. - Watters, Walter Patterson - (Creative Writing, Fiction), 1968-1970 (Box 420, Folder 3622)
    - Southern University - Mackey, William - (Playwright), 1968-1971 (Box 421, Folder 3623)
    - Spelman College - Intercollegiate Chorus - (Shaw, Robert), 1967-1968 (Box 421, Folder 3624)
    - Stanford University - American Studies - Kishimoto, Hideyo - (Visiting Scholar), 1951-1954 (Box 421, Folder 3625)
    - Stanford University - American Studies - Nakaya, Kenichi - (Visiting Scholar), 1953-1954 (Box 421, Folder 3626)
    - Stanford University - Breitrose, Henry - (Film Critic), 1965-1966 (Box 421, Folder 3627)
    - Stanford University - Drama, 1964-1970 (Box 421, Folder 3628)
    - Stanford University - Drama, 1964-1970 (Box 421, Folder 3629)
    - Stanford University - Drama, 1964-1970 (Box 421, Folder 3630)
    - Stanford University - Gaines, Ernest - (Creative Writing, Fiction), 1969-1971 (Box 421, Folder 3631)
    - Stanford University - Coheen, John D. - (Philosophy in Asia and Western Europe), 1955-1958 (Box 421, Folder 3632)
    - Stanford University - Hoover Institute - Turkish History - (Enver Ziya Karal, Frederick P. Latimer, Jr.), 1956-1960 (Box 422, Folder 3633)
    - Stanford University - Hoover Institute - Turkish History - (Enver Ziya Karal, Frederick P. Latimer, Jr.), 1956-1960 (Box 422, Folder 3634)
    - Stanford University - Japanese Poetry - (Robert Brower, Earl Miner), 1956-1959 (Box 422, Folder 3635)
    - Stanford University - Japanese Studies, 1952-1953, 1955-1965, 1968 (Box 422, Folder 3636)
    - Stanford University - Japanese Studies - Yashiro Yukio - (Japanese Art in America), 1954-1957 (Box 422, Folder 3637)
    - Stanford University - Japanese University Management - (Seminars), 1955-1961 (Box 422, Folder 3638)
    - Stanford University - Japanese University Management - (Seminars), 1955-1961 (Box 422, Folder 3639)
    - Stanford University - Konishi, Jin'ichi - (Visiting Scholar, Literature), 1957-1959 (Box 422, Folder 3640)
    - Stanford University - North, Robert C. - (Indian Literature), 1953-1956 (Box 423, Folder 3641)
    - Stanford University - North, Robert C. - "Trends in Contemporary Indian Literature", 1955 (Box 423, Folder 3642)
    - Starr King School for the Ministry - Print Collection, 1956-1961 (Box 423, Folder 3643)
    - State University College, New Paltz - Environmental Theatre, 1970 (Box 423, Folder 3644)
    - State University of New York at Albany - Mirabelli, Eugene F., Jr. - (Creative Writing, Fiction), 1969-1972 (Box 423, Folder 3645)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo - Barth, John - (Creative Writing, Fiction), 1964-1969, 1971 (Box 423, Folder 3646)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo - Logan, John - (Creative Writing, Poetry), 1968-1970 (Box 423, Folder 3647)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook - Paik, Nam June - (Video Artist), 1967-1969 (Box 423, Folder 3648)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook - Paik, Nam June - (Video Artist), 1967-1969 (Box 423, Folder 3649)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook - Ross, Stanley Q. - (History at New Mexico), 1967-1970, 1972 (Box 423, Folder 3650)
    - State University Teachers College, Oneonta - Frost, James A. - (American Studies) - (Travel Grant, Japan), 1958-1960 (Box 424, Folder 3651)
    - Stetsen University - Florida Music Festival Institute - Scholarships, 1965-1968 (Box 424, Folder 3652)
    - Stevenson, Elizabeth - (Lafcadio Hearn Biography), 1959 (Box 424, Folder 3653)
    - Strand, Mark - (Creative Writing, Poetry), 1968-1970 (Box 424, Folder 3654)
    - Style in Language Conference, 1967-1971 (Box 424, Folder 3655)
    - Summer Institute of Linguisties - Pike, Kenneth J., 1952-1959, 1967 (Box 424, Folder 3656)
    - Summer Institute of Linguisties - Pike, Kenneth J., 1952-1959, 1967 (Box 424, Folder 3657)
    - Summer Institute of Linguisties - Pike, Kenneth J. - "Structure: A Unified Theory of Language and Behavior", 1953 (Box 424, Folder 3658)
    - Swan, Jon - (Playwright), 1968-1971 (Box 424, Folder 3659)
    - Swarthmore College - Brandt, Richard - (Philosophy), 1958-1960 (Box 424, Folder 3660)
    - Swarthmore College - Brandt, Richard - (Philosophy), 1961-1962 (Box 425, Folder 3661)
    - Sweet Briar College - Masur, Gerhard - (European History), 1952-1957, 1961-1962 (Box 425, Folder 3662)
    - Sweet Briar College - Masur, Gerhard - (European History), 1952-1957, 1961-1962 (Box 425, Folder 3663)
    - Swenson, May - (Creative Writing, Poetry), 1967-1969 (Box 425, Folder 3664)
    - Syracuse University - Booth, Philip - (Creative Writing, Poetry), 1966-1969 (Box 425, Folder 3665)
    - Symphony Orchestras - Composers in Residence, 1965-1970 (Box 425, Folder 3666)
    - Symphony Orchestras - Young Composers Program, 1964-1969 (Box 425, Folder 3667)
    - Symphony Orchestras - Young Composers Program - Evaluation (A-Z), 1967 (Box 425, Folder 3668)
    - Taylor, Douglas - (Playwright), 1966-1969 (Box 425, Folder 3669)
    - Television Survey - Hamburger, Philip, 1950, 1952 (Box 425, Folder 3670)
    - Tennessee State University - Opera - (Treemonisha by Scott Joplin), 1969-1970 (Box 426, Folder 3671)
    - Terry, Megan - (Playwright), 1967-1970 (Box 426, Folder 3672)
    - Texas Christian University - Graves, John, 1969-1971 (Box 426, Folder 3673)
    - Texas State Historical Association - American History, 1942-1952, 1954 (Box 426, Folder 3674)
    - Texas State Historical Association - American History, 1942-1952, 1954 (Box 426, Folder 3675)
    - Texas State Historical Association - American History, 1942-1952, 1954 (Box 426, Folder 3676)
    - Theatre Company of Boston - (Production of New Plays), 1964-1971 (Box 426, Folder 3677)
    - Theatre Company of Boston - Scrapbooks, 1968-1969 (Box 426, Folder 3678)
    - Theatre in the Street, 1964-1970, 1972 (Box 427, Folder 3679)
    - Theatre in the Street, 1964-1970, 1972 (Box 427, Folder 3680)
    - Tibetan Studies - (Conference), June 1959-1961, 1966 (Box 427, Folder 3681)
    - Tibetan Studies - (Conference), June 1959-1961, 1966 (Box 427, Folder 3682)
    - Tibetan Studies - (Conference), June 1959-1961, 1966 (Box 427, Folder 3683)
    - Tibetan Studies - Supplemental Material, 1956-1959; 5 Items (Box 428, Folder 3684)
    - Tougaloo College - Library, 1968; 5 Items (Box 428, Folder 3685)
    - Trans-Pacific Conference on Book Publishing - (University of Hawaii), 1962 (Box 428, Folder 3686)
    - Trinity Square Playhouse - (Public School Performance), 1965-1968 (Box 428, Folder 3687)
    - Tucker, Robert Charles - (Chinese Communist Philosophy), 1958-1959 (Box 428, Folder 3688)
    - Tufts University - Bauer, Arnold J. - (History) - (Travel Grant, Chile), 1966 (Box 428, Folder 3689)
    - Tufts University - Burch, George B. - (Vedanta) - (Travel Grant, India), 1952-1956 (Box 428, Folder 3690)
    - Tufts University - Burch, George B. - (Vedanta) - (Travel Grant, India), 1952-1956 (Box 428, Folder 3691)
    - Tufts University - Burch, George B. - (Contemporary Indian Philosophy), 1959-1962, 1964 (Box 428, Folder 3692)
    - Tufts University - Wright, Thomas C. - (History) - (Travel Grant, Chile), 1967, 1969 (Box 428, Folder 3693)
    - Tulane Drama Review, 1962-1967 (Box 429, Folder 3694)
    - Tulane Drama Review, 1962-1967 (Box 429, Folder 3695)
    - Tulane University - Drama Criticism - (Critics Tour), 1962-1965 (Box 429, Folder 3696)
    - Unger, Robert Louis - (Playwright), 1966-1968 (Box 429, Folder 3697)
    - Union Theological Seminary - Martin, J. Alfred, Jr. - (Travel Grant, Asia), 1960-1962 (Box 429, Folder 3698)
    - Union Theological Seminary - Religious Drama, 1953-1959 (Box 429, Folder 3699)
    - Union Theological Seminary - Religious Drama, 1953-1959 (Box 429, Folder 3700)
    - Union Theological Seminary - Religious Drama, 1960-1962 (Box 430, Folder 3701)
    - Union Theological Seminary - Suzuki, D.T. - (Visiting Lecturer, Zen Studies), 1950-1952 (Box 430, Folder 3702)
    - Union Theological Seminary - Theatre Criticism Training - (Driver, Thomas), 1967-1969 (Box 430, Folder 3703)
    - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Libraries - (Land, Ray), 1957, 1959-1960 (Box 430, Folder 3704)
    - United States Army - Language School - (Cowan, J. Milton), 1955-1956 (Box 430, Folder 3705)
    - University of Alabama - Philosophy of Law - (Jenkins, Iredell), 1955-1959 (Box 430, Folder 3706)
    - University of Alaska - Northrip, Charles - (Educational Television), 1969-1971 (Box 430, Folder 3707)
    - University of Arizona - Indian Art, 1958-1960 (Box 430, Folder 3708)
    - University of Arizona - Indian Art, 1961-1965, 1976 (Box 431, Folder 3709)
    - University of Arizona - Indian Art - Reports, 1959-1962; 4 Items (Box 431, Folder 3710)
    - University of Arkansas - Friedman, Frederick G. - (Peasant Culture), 1950-1956 (Box 431, Folder 3711)
    - University of Arkansas - Friedman, Frederick G. - (Peasant Culture), 1950-1956 (Box 431, Folder 3712)
    - University of Arkansas - Friedman, Frederick G. - (Peasant Culture), 1950-1956 (Box 431, Folder 3713)
    - University of Arkansas - Friedman, Frederick G. - (Peasant Culture), 1950-1956 (Box 431, Folder 3714)
    - University of Arkansas - Friedman, Frederick G. - Reports, 1954; 3 Items (Box 432, Folder 3715)
    - University of Buffalo - Creative Music Associates - (Lurkas Foss, Allen D. Sapp), 1963-1969 (Box 432, Folder 3716)
    - University of Buffalo - Creative Music Associates - (Lurkas Foss, Allen D. Sapp), 1963-1969 (Box 432, Folder 3717)
    - University of Buffalo - Creative Music Associates - (Lurkas Foss, Allen D. Sapp), 1963-1969 (Box 432, Folder 3718)
    - University of California - African Art Exhibit, 1969-1970 (Box 432, Folder 3719)
    - University of California - Chen, Kenneth - (Travel Grant, Tibetan Studies), 1959 (Box 432, Folder 3720)
    - University of California - Chung, Hazel - (Oriental Dance), 1961-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 432, Folder 3721)
    - University of California - City Planning Study - (Barclay G. Jones, Stephen W. Jacobs), 1958-1959 (Box 432, Folder 3722)
    - University of California - City Planning Study - (Barclay G. Jones, Stephen W. Jacobs), 1960-1964 (Box 433, Folder 3723)
    - University of California - City Planning Study - Supplementary Material, 1959-1960 (Box 433, Folder 3724)
    - University of California - City Planning Study - Supplementary Material, 1959-1960 (Box 433, Folder 3725)
    - University of California - City Planning Study - Supplementary Material, 1959-1960 (Box 433, Folder 3726)
    - University of California - Dugger, Ronald - (Biography of Lyndon B. Johnson), 1969-1971 (Box 433, Folder 3727)
    - University of California - English Language Teaching in The Philippines, 1955-March 1957 (Box 433, Folder 3728)
    - University of California - English Language Teaching in The Philippines, 1955-March 1957 (Box 433, Folder 3729)
    - University of California - English Language Teaching in The Philippines, 1955-March 1957 (Box 433, Folder 3730)
    - University of California - English Language Teaching in The Philippines, April 1957-1967, 1969 (Box 434, Folder 3731)
    - University of California - English Language Teaching in The Philippines, April 1957-1967, 1969 (Box 434, Folder 3732)
    - University of California - English Language Teaching in The Philippines, April 1957-1967, 1969 (Box 434, Folder 3733)
    - University of California - English Language Teaching in The Philippines, April 1957-1967, 1969 (Box 434, Folder 3734)